- Dear diary...
亲爱的日记...
- Hey, whatcha doing?
嘿，你在做什么？
- Nothing.
没什么。
Wait, what are you doing in here?
等等，你在这里做什么？
- Oh, I'm in here all the time, usually when you're not.
哦，我经常在这里，通常是你不在的时候。
- Oh. Get out.
哦。出去。
- What's behind your back?
你背后藏着什么？
- Nothing, get out.
没什么，出去。
- Oh, 'cause it said diary, and you said, "Dear diary."
哦，因为上面写着‘日记’，而你说了‘亲爱的日记’。
So I figured it was a diary.
所以我以为这是日记。
- It's not a diary.
- 这不是日记。
- Ooh, you have a diary? - No.
- 哦，你有日记吗？ - 没有。
- Anything in there about us?
- 里面有关于我们的内容吗？
- Diaries are for private thoughts
- 日记是用来记录私密想法的
like rooms with signs on the door that say, "No boys allowed."
就像门上贴着“男生止步”的房间一样。
- Huh, is that new? - Yeah, I think that's new. [All talking over each other]
- 嗯，那是新的吗？ - 是的，我觉得那是新的。 [大家同时说话]
- No!
- 不！
It's been there since I moved in.
从我搬进来那天起就在那儿了。
Look, I respect your privacy and I would really
听着，我尊重你的隐私，如果你们也能尊重我的，我会非常感激。
appreciate it if you would respect mine.
别担心。你可以信任我们。
- Don't worry. You can trust us.
- 别担心，你可以信任我们。
- Totally. - Absolutely.
- 当然。 - 绝对。
- Coast is clear.
- 安全无虞。
- We got to find that diary and see what she writes about us.
- 我们得找到那本日记，看看她写了我们什么。
- No diary, just this weird ear-warmer thing.
- 没有日记，只有这个奇怪的耳暖。
- These aren't ear-warmers.
- 这些不是耳暖。
They're an old-timey toothache cure.
它们是旧时的牙痛疗法。
- No, they're workout bands.
- 不，它们是运动发带。
Whoo! - What? What?
喔！ - 什么？什么？
- This is not what it looks like.
- 这不是你们想的那样。
- We didn't come in here to play with your workout bands.
- 我们进来不是为了玩你的运动带。
- Those are my sports bras.
- 那些是我的运动文胸。
- Ew, that was on my face.
- 呃，那东西刚在我脸上。
- Gross, mine too! - Just go!
- 恶心，我的也是！ - 快走！
I have a very long and angry diary entry to write.
我有一篇又长又愤怒的日记要写。
- Oh, by the way, where do you keep your diary?
- 哦，顺便问一下，你的日记放哪儿了？
- Yeah, we looked everywhere for it.
- 是啊，我们到处都找过了。
- You were in Dawn's room again without permission, huh?
- 你又未经允许进Dawn的房间了，是吧？
all: Yep.
所有人: 是的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ One, two ♪ ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪
- Yeah, Mae, I'm leaving now.
是的，梅，我现在要走了。
Yeah, I'll just meet you at the ice cream place
好的，我会在那个以说唱歌手命名的冰淇淋店和你碰面。
named after the rapper.
不是Scoop Dogg，是Cone-ye West。
No, not Scoop Dogg, Cone-ye West.
你听到了吗？
- Did you hear that?
是的，她要去Cone-ye West。
- Yeah, she's going to Cone-ye West.
那地方远不如Wu-Tang Cone好。
That place is nowhere near as good as Wu-Tang Cone.
你在说什么？
- What are you talking about?
那里只有两种尺寸，Biggie或Smalls。
There's only two sizes there, Biggie or Smalls.
伙计们，我不知道。我们真的应该这么做吗？
- Guys, I don't know. Should we really be doing this?
The sign does say, "No boys allowed."
牌子上确实写着，“不许男孩进入。”
- Now it says, "No, boys allowed."
现在它写着，“不，男孩可以进入。”
- Whoa, word magic.
哇，文字游戏。
- Yikes, she is really mad at us.
哎呀，她真的对我们很生气。
- You know what?
你知道吗？
Words do hurt.
言语确实伤人。
- Hey, look, not all of it's about us.
嘿，看，并非所有事情都与我们有关。
- Dear diary, this is top secret.
亲爱的日记，这是最高机密。
all: Ooh.
哦。
- Yesterday, I went to the school nurse,
and she told me I have a highly contagious mouth fungus.
all: Ew.
- She said it would probably go away
in a couple of weeks,
so I'm not telling anyone about it.
It's gross and itchy,
and it makes my tongue all hairy.
The only thing that makes it feel better
is scratching it with the end of my diary pen.
- Diary pen!
日记笔！
- Hairy tongue, search.
毛舌，搜索。
[all yell]
[众人惊叫]
- Mm, this Mackles'more is so good.
- 嗯，这个Mackles'more真好吃。
- Not as good as that Kendrick Lamarshmallow.
- 没有Kendrick Lamarshmallow好吃。
Oh, hey, guys.
哦，嘿，伙计们。
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嘿。- 你好。
- 'Sup?
- 怎么了？
- Oh, this ice cream is so good.
- 哦，这冰淇淋太好吃了。
It's like a party on my tongue.
就像我的舌头上开派对。
Oh, here, try some. - No, thanks.
哦，来，尝一点。 - 不用了，谢谢。
- Nicky, you would love it. - I'm good.
- 尼基，你会喜欢的。 - 我很好。
- Dicky? - Ew, no.
- 迪基？ - 呃，不要。
- Okay, what's going on?
- 好吧，怎么了？
You guys love ice cream named after rappers.
你们不是喜欢以说唱歌手的名字命名的冰淇淋吗？
- Yeah, but, um...
- 是啊，但是，嗯...
- We just had some country music breakfast foods.
- 我们刚吃了一些乡村音乐主题的早餐食品。
- Yes, the Rascal Flapjacks were very filling.
- 是的，那些“叛逆松饼”非常饱腹。
- Oh, come on, guys.
- 哦，拜托，伙计们。
There's always room for ice cream.
吃冰淇淋总是有空间的。
- No, thanks. We're so full, it's hairy.
- 不了，谢谢。我们太饱了，简直撑得慌。
I mean, scary.
我是说，吓人。
- Well, I'm full too.
- 嗯，我也吃得很饱。
So I'm just gonna leave this right here
所以我就把这放在这儿，
in case you guys change your mind. Come on, Mae, let's go up to my room.
万一你们改变主意。来吧，梅，我们去我房间。
- That was close.
- 好险。
- Yeah, reading her diary was the only thing
- 是啊，偷看她的日记是我们
that stood between us and a hairy tongue.
避免舌头长毛的唯一办法。
- What's up, boys?
- 怎么了，伙计们？
- [gasps] Is that Kendrick Lamarshmallow?
- [倒抽一口气] 那是肯德里克·拉马尔棉花糖吗？
both: Dibs!
我先说的！
[both talking at once]
（两人同时说话）
[all groaning]
（所有人呻吟）
[laughter]
（笑声）
- They totally fell for it.
他们完全上当了。
- And now for phase two, the tongue wig.
现在是第二阶段，舌头假发。
- No, I think phase one sold it.
不，我觉得第一阶段已经足够了。
- So are you going to make more fake diary entries?
所以你打算继续写假的日记条目吗？
- Uh, absolutely.
呃，当然。
I know they're going to keep reading it.
我知道他们会继续看的。
And if I can't trust the boys, I don't want them to be able to trust each other.
如果我不能信任这些男孩，我也不希望他们能够互相信任。
- Are you sure?
- 你确定吗？
'Cause this is pretty scary.
因为这真的很可怕。
- Now boys allowed.
- 现在不允许男孩进入。
- Dear diary, what I found out about my brothers
亲爱的日记，前几天我发现
the other day really shocked me.
关于我的兄弟们的事情真的让我震惊。
They always used to be a united threesome, but now?
他们曾经总是团结的三人组，但现在呢？
Two of them are turning on the other,
其中两个正在对付另一个，
and what they plan to do to him frightens me.
他们计划对他做的事情让我害怕。
They're going to go after what he prizes the most,
他们将针对他最珍视的东西，
and he'll have no idea because it'll happen
而且他将毫无察觉，因为这会在他最意想不到的时候发生。
when he least expects it.
我是说，我想警告他，但他最近对我有点刻薄。
I mean, I'd like to warn him, but he's been
也许如果他对我好一点，我会帮他。
kind of mean to me lately.
哦，好吧，我们走着瞧。
Maybe if he were nicer, I'd help him out.
今天的足球训练很好。
Oh, well, we'll see.
教练说我--
Soccer practice was good today.
- 等等，教练说什么了？
Coach says I'm--
- 教练说什么重要吗？
- Wait, what did coach say?
你们俩有什么要告诉我的吗？
- Who cares what coach said?
没有，你和Dicky有什么要告诉我的吗？
Is there anything that you two would like to tell me?
你们两个有什么想告诉我的吗？
- No, do you and Dicky have anything you'd like to tell me?
- 没有，你和Dicky有什么想告诉我的吗？
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- 我不知道你在说什么。
- Me neither.
- 我也是。
- All right, this is silly.
- 好吧，这太傻了。
- Yeah, we all trust each other, right?
- 是的，我们都互相信任，对吧？
- Right. - Right.
- 对。 - 对。
These two are definitely up to something.
这两人肯定在搞什么鬼。
- I don't trust these two at all.
- 我完全不信任这两人。
- I really want to know what coach said.
- 我真的很想知道教练说了什么。
- All right, boys, lights out.
- 好了，伙计们，熄灯。
Sweet dreams.
做个好梦。
- Well, you heard her.
- 嗯，你们听到了。
Guess it's time for total darkness.
看来是时候完全黑暗了。
- Where things can happen without us seeing them coming.
- 这样事情可以在我们不知不觉中发生。
- But those things will never happen, right?
- 但那些事情永远不会发生，对吧？
- No. - Of course not.
- 不会。 - 当然不会。
[bed creaks] [all scream]
[床吱吱作响] [大家尖叫]
[vacuum whirring]
[吸尘器嗡嗡声]
[vacuum turns off]
[吸尘器关闭]
[bed creaks]
[床吱嘎作响]
- Oh...
- 哦...
guess my bed squeaks a little.
看来我的床有点吱吱响。
- You heard me, boys. I said lights out.
- 你们听到了，孩子们。我说了熄灯。
[bed creaks] [all scream]
[床吱嘎作响] [所有人尖叫]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- ♪ La, la-la-la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦-啦-啦 ♪
- Five, carry the two, divide that by three equals...
- 五，进二，除以三等于...
I hate homework.
我讨厌做作业。
- That's the same answer I got.
- 我得到的也是这个答案。
- Dawn, Dawn, Dawn, or Dawn to the third power
- 晨曦，晨曦，晨曦，或者说是晨曦的三次方
as us math guys like to say.
我们数学家喜欢这么说。
Why don't you take a little break and let me
为什么不稍微休息一下，让我
handle the homework situation?
来处理这个作业问题？
In fact, the Rickulator has already completed
实际上，Rickulator已经完成了
your assignments for the week.
你这周的所有作业。
You know you can count on me to get you an A.
你知道你可以依靠我帮你拿到A。
Well, a B-plus to make it seem like you did it.
嗯，为了让你看起来像是自己做的，我会给你个B+。
- Why would you do my homework?
- 你为什么要帮我做作业？
That falls in the... you broke something,
这属于那种...你弄坏了什么，
need something, or have something to hide category.
需要什么，或者有什么要隐瞒的类别。
- What? Hogwash.
- 什么？胡说八道。
- What's hogwash?
- 什么是胡说八道？
- It's similar to "balderdash."
- 类似于“胡言乱语”。
And doing your homework is just what kind,
而帮你做作业，正是那种，
loving siblings do.
有爱心的兄弟姐妹会做的事。
For example, you'd look out for me if you knew
比如说，如果你知道
I was in imminent danger or if someone
我有迫在眉睫的危险，或者有人
was threatening what I prize the most
威胁到我最珍视的东西
like my perfect attendance record.
比如我完美的出勤记录。
You'd tell me, right?
你会告诉我的，对吧？
- Of course.
当然。
- So anything you want to tell me now?
所以现在有什么想告诉我的吗？
- Nope.
没有。
- Well, if anything comes up, I'll be upstairs
嗯，如果有任何事情发生，我会在楼上
working on your music history report.
帮你做音乐史报告。
Just remember, I'll always have your Bach.
记住，我永远支持你。
See what I did there?
看我这话说得怎么样？
- Wow, this is going way better than I thought.
哇，这比我想象的要顺利多了。
Oh, and I smell chocolate chip paranoia
哦，我还闻到了厨房传来的巧克力碎片带来的紧张气氛。
coming from the kitchen.
从厨房飘来的。
- Oh, hello, ladies.
噢，你们好，女士们。
Don't mind me, I'm just baking some of Dawn's favorite
别介意我，我只是在烤道恩最喜欢的巧克力碎片松饼。
chocolate chip muffins.
嗯。
- Mm. - Mmm.
嗯～
These are delicious.
这些很美味。
- Can you guess the secret ingredient?
你能猜到秘密成分是什么吗？
- Sugar? - No.
糖？
- Flour? - No.
不是。
- Baking soda. - No.
面粉？
- Chocolate chips?
巧克力碎片？
- Those aren't secret ingredients!
那些可不是秘密成分！
- Shrimp? - Trust!
虾？ - 信任！
Trust is the secret ingredient!
信任才是秘密成分！
Enjoy.
请享用。
- Why would you make us muffins?
你为什么要给我们做松饼？
- I just enjoy doing nice things for nice people,
我只是喜欢为好人做好事，
like my nice sister Dawn.
比如我善良的姐姐Dawn。
- Hogwash!
胡说八道！
It's like balderdash.
简直是胡言乱语。
- No, it's true.
不，这是真的。
I'm just looking out for my sis
我只是关心我的妹妹，
like she always looks out for me.
就像她总是关心我一样。
For example, if you knew someone or...
比如说，如果你知道有人或者...
two people were threatening what I love most...
两个人威胁到我最珍爱的东西...
Say, my perfectly seasoned cast iron skillet,
比如说，我那调味得恰到好处的铸铁煎锅，
I could trust you to warn me, right?
我可以相信你会提醒我，对吧？
- Well, there is something I do need to warn you about.
嗯，确实有件事我需要提醒你。
- Yes?
是吗？
- We're gonna eat all these muffins.
我们要把这些松饼都吃掉。
- Wait, isn't there anything else you want to tell me?
- 等等，你没有什么其他想告诉我的吗？
- Nope.
- 没有。
Two down, one to go.
两个下肚，还剩一个。
- Hey, girls, whatcha eating?
- 嘿，姑娘们，你们在吃什么？
- Oh, Nicky made muffins.
- 哦，尼基做了松饼。
I think there's one left in the kitchen.
我想厨房里还剩一个。
both: Dibs!
两人: 我要了！
- There she is, my favorite sister.
- 她来了，我最喜欢的妹妹。
- She's your only sister.
- 她是你唯一的妹妹。
- Aren't we all sisters?
- 我们不都是姐妹吗？
Uh, Dawn, I brought you a gift.
呃，Dawn，我给你带了个礼物。
- Why?
为什么？
- I just felt like giving you something,
我就是想给你点什么，
you know, like you'd give me a warning if you knew
你知道的，就像如果你知道
someone wanted to take away what I prize most.
有人想夺走我最珍视的东西，你会提醒我一样。
Like my luscious locks.
比如我这头浓密的秀发。
- Sure.
当然。
Um, Dicky, this is my lamp.
嗯，Dicky，这是我的台灯。
- I knew you'd love it.
我就知道你会喜欢它。
So now that I gave you something,
既然我已经给了你东西，
is there something you would like to give me?
你有什么想给我的吗？
Like information?
比如信息？
- Yep. - Really?
- 是的。 - 真的吗？
- Oh, did I say "yep"?
- 哦，我说了“是的”吗？
I meant nope.
我是说“不是”。
Three for three, doesn't get any better than this.
三连胜，没有比这更好的了。
Writing fake diary entries to mess with my brothers
写假日记条目来捉弄我兄弟
is the best idea I've ever had.
是我有史以来最好的主意。
I now have a homework servant, a muffin chef,
我现在有了一个作业仆人，一个松饼厨师，
and a brighter room.
还有一个更明亮的房间。
- I can't wait until my brother's old enough
- 我迫不及待想等到我哥哥大到能读我的假日记。
to read my fake diary.
等他大到能读我的假日记。
Mmm, we're out of muffins.
嗯，我们的松饼吃完了。
- Relax, I know where we can go get some more.
- 放松，我知道我们可以去哪里再买一些。
- Mmm, s'mores sound good.
- 嗯，烤棉花糖夹心饼干听起来不错。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
Let's get Nicky to make some of those too.
让尼基也做一些那种饼干吧。
Just when I thought it couldn't get any better,
就在我以为不能再好了的时候，
it got s'more better.
它变得更好了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Fake diary entries?
假的日记条目？
The other boys are never gonna believe this.
其他男孩们绝不会相信这个。
- I believe it.
我相信。
- I believe it too.
我也相信。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Mae's heavier than I thought.
梅比我预想的要重。
- What are you guys doing in here?
你们在这里做什么？
- I was trying to get info about what you guys were gonna do to me.
我正试图了解你们打算对我做什么。
- Me, too, but now we know everything was all made up
我也是，但现在我们知道一切都是编造的
so Dawn could manipulate us into turning on each other.
所以道恩可以操纵我们互相攻击。
- I can't believe she double-crossed us.
- 我真不敢相信她出卖了我们。
- Yeah, who would go to such lengths just to
- 是啊，谁会为了背叛某人的信任而做到这种地步？
betray someone's trust?
- 你知道吗，我觉得是时候我们开始合作了
- You know, I think it's time we start working together
- 来报复Dawn。
to get Dawn back.
- 没错，我有个计划。
- Yeah, and I have a plan.
- 但首先，你能给我们做些烤棉花糖夹心饼干吗？
But first, could you make us some s'mores?
- 我快饿死了。
I'm starving.
- 我本想在豆袋椅上吃点零食，
I thought I'd have a snack in the beanbag chair,
- 结果发现，这些豆子不是真的。
but turns out, these weren't real beans.
- ♪ 哦，哦 ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦 ♪
[knock at door]
[敲门声]
- Who is it?
谁呀？
- It's Dicky.
是Dicky。
You asleep yet?
你睡着了吗？
- Yes.
是的。
- Okay.
好的。
Do you know when you'll be awake?
你知道你什么时候会醒吗？
- I'm awake now, Dicky.
我现在醒了，Dicky。
- I thought you just said you were asleep.
我以为你刚说你睡着了。
- Okay, just come in!
好的，进来吧！
- There she is, my sister from the same mister.
她在这里，我的亲姐妹。
- What do you want?
你想要什么？
- I came in here to apologize for reading your diary.
我来这里是为了为偷看你的日记道歉。
- You did what?
你做了什么？
- And to thank you for what you wrote.
并且感谢你写的内容。
Look, I don't want to make too big of a deal out of this,
听着，我不想把这件事搞得太大，
but your most private thoughts saved my life.
但你的最私密的想法救了我的命。
Now I know about Ricky and Nicky's plot to betray me.
现在我知道了Ricky和Nicky的背叛计划。
You're my hero, and thanks to you,
你是我的英雄，多亏了你，
I'm about to go mess with them before they can mess with me.
我打算在他们对付我之前先去搞他们。
- Mae, remember how I said it couldn't get any better
Mae，记得我说的，事情不可能比之前更好了，
from when it got better after being better?
从那之后变得更好了？
It just got better.
现在变得更好了。
- Did I miss it?
我错过了吗？
- No, the boys haven't come down yet.
没有，那两个男孩还没下来。
This should be good, though.
不过这应该会很有趣。
Dicky really meant business last night.
Dicky昨晚真的很认真。
- He did?
真的吗？
Are you nervous at all?
你一点儿都不紧张吗？
What if he does something really bad?
万一他做了什么真的很糟糕的事呢？
- Nah, how bad could it be?
不会的，能有多糟糕？
[boys scream]
[男孩们尖叫]
Don't worry, it's just a harmless prank.
别担心，这只是个无害的恶作剧。
It's not like they're out for blood.
又不是他们要见血。
- They're out for blood!
他们是要见血的！
- Oh, hi, Dawn and Mae.
哦，嗨，Dawn和Mae。
How's your morning going?
你们早上过得怎么样？
- Okay.
还行。
- Can't complain.
没什么可抱怨的。
- That's terrific.
- 那太好了。
We don't have any hair!
- 我们没有头发！
- Hey, you know who else doesn't have any hair?
- 嘿，你知道还有谁没有头发吗？
Vin Diesel, and he's doing okay.
范·迪塞尔，他也过得不错。
- I may not be fast, but I'm furious!
- 我可能不快，但我很愤怒！
- Wait, stop!
- 等等，停下！
The only reason I shaved your heads was because
我剃光你们头的原因只是因为
I thought you were gonna shave mine.
我以为你们会剃光我的。
- Why would you think that?
- 你为什么会这么想？
- Because I read in Dawn's diary that you were
- 因为我在Dawn的日记里读到，你们要
gonna take the thing that I prized most.
要拿走我最珍视的东西。
- Hiya.
嗨呀。
- Dawn, why would you write a lie like that
晨曦，你为什么要写那样的谎言
in your diary?
在你的日记里？
- Because you guys invaded my privacy,
因为你们侵犯了我的隐私，
and I wanted to teach you a lesson.
我想给你们一个教训。
So I wrote some fake stuff in my diary
所以我在日记里写了一些假的东西
to turn you against each other.
让你们互相猜疑。
[all gasp]
[大家都惊讶地吸气]
- Why would you do that?
你为什么要这么做？
- I am shocked.
我感到震惊。
- And bald.
而且还秃了。
- I never thought my diary would cause things
我从没想过我的日记会让事情
to get this out of control.
变得如此失控。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
- We appreciate that, Dawn.
我们理解你的道歉，Dawn。
But all the "I'm sorrys" in the world
但世界上所有的'对不起'都无法
won't bring our hair back.
让我们的头发回来。
- I know, and I feel horrible.
我知道，我感到非常糟糕。
I promise I'll find a way to make it up to you.
我保证我会找到办法补偿你们的。
- Honestly, Dawn, I don't know how
老实说，Dawn，我不知道怎么
that would be possible.
这可能实现。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- She totally bought it.
她完全相信了。
- Who knew the flesh-colored swim caps
谁知道爸爸在店里卖不出去的肉色泳帽
Dad couldn't sell at the store would finally come in handy?
最后会派上用场？
- My bald cap's starting to itch. Can I take it off?
我的秃头帽开始痒了。我能摘掉吗？
- I think we should keep it on for the rest of the day
我觉得我们应该戴着它一整天
and see how guilty we can make Dawn feel.
看看我们能让Dawn感到多内疚。
In fact, let's start a wish list of stuff we can
事实上，让我们开始列一个愿望清单，
guilt Dawn into giving us.
让Dawn感到内疚，从而给我们买。
Number 370, a hot tub for our bedroom.
第370号，我们卧室的按摩浴缸。
- Yeah, I've got some foot issues you guys
- 是的，我有些脚的问题，你们不会想参与的。
don't want any part of.
- 呃，为什么不弄三个按摩浴缸呢？
- Uh, why not make it three hot tubs?
- 嗨，伙计们。
- Hi, guys.
Dawn仍然对整个假日记的事情感到非常糟糕。
Dawn still feels terrible about the whole fake diary thing.
- 她应该的。
- She should. - It was terrible.
- 那真的很糟糕。
- It could've been me.
- 那本可能是我。
- But she thinks she found a way to make it up to you.
- 但她认为她找到了补偿你们的方法。
- Is it a monkey on a motorcycle?
- 是摩托车上的猴子吗？
If not, put it on the list.
如果不是，就把它列在清单上。
- Dawn, come on in.
- 道恩，进来吧。
- After some deep thought and reflection,
- 经过深思熟虑和反省，
I decided that if my fake diary caused Nicky and Ricky
我决定如果我的假日记让尼基和里基秃头了，那么我也应该秃头。
to be bald, then I deserve to be bald too.
- 你做了什么？ - 有那么糟糕吗？
- What did you do? - Is it that bad?
- 太可怕了。 - 糟透了。
- Terrible. - Awful.
- 咕噜姆！
- Gollum!
- 嗯，你们看起来也不怎么样。
- Well, you guys don't look so good either.
- 实际上...
both: Actually...
实际上...
- Bald caps? - Sorry.
- 秃头帽？ - 对不起。
All three of us overheard you guys talking in your room.
我们三个人无意中听到你们在房间里的谈话。
- What? When? - Last night.
- 什么？什么时候？ - 昨晚。
- And by the way, Mae, you're heavier than you look.
- 顺便说一句，Mae，你比看起来要重。
- You were in my room again?
- 你又在我的房间里了？
- Yeah, and it's a good thing, 'cause we found out
- 是的，还好我们进去了，因为我们发现
those diary entries were fake.
那些日记条目是假的。
- Liar!
- 骗子！
- So we're giving you a taste of your own medicine.
- 所以我们现在也让你们尝尝自己的苦果。
How's it taste, Dawn?
Dawn，这味道如何？
- Taste!
味道！
- So I shaved my head for nothing?
那我剃光头岂不是白剃了？
Oh, this is bad. This is so bad!
哦，这太糟糕了。真是糟透了！
I have to go to school tomorrow.
我明天还得去学校。
What did I do?
我做了什么？
- You know what?
你知道吗？
The whole fake head shaving plan was mine in the first place.
其实一开始整个假剃头的计划就是我出的主意。
I know what I have to do to make this right.
我知道我该怎么做才能弥补这一切。
[buzzing]
（嗡嗡声）
- Wait, Dicky, no!
- 等等，迪基，不要！
I was faking it too.
我也是在假装。
- This story has more twists than a cinnamon roll.
- 这个故事的转折比肉桂卷还多。
- Cinnamon rolls only have one twist. - But it's a pretty big twist!
- 肉桂卷只有一个转折。- 但那个转折挺大的！
- How did you know we were faking it?
- 你怎么知道我们是在假装？
- Mae and I overheard you guys in here talking about your Dawn guilt wish list.
- 我和梅在旁边听见了你们在这里讨论对道恩的愧疚清单。
- You were eavesdropping on our private conversation?
- 你们在偷听我们的私人对话？
- Private? The pass-through was completely open.
- 私人？传菜口完全是开着的。
- Yeah, we said,
- 是啊，我们还说了好几次，
"Uh, guys, we're right here," several times.
“嗯，伙计们，我们就在旁边。”
- It's still an invasion of our privacy.
- 这仍然是对我们隐私的侵犯。
- You know, when you think about it,
- 你知道，当你仔细想一想，
we invaded your privacy, you invaded our privacy.
我们侵犯了你的隐私，你侵犯了我们的隐私。
It's kind of funny.
这有点好笑。
- [laughs] - Yeah, I guess it is.
- [笑] - 是的，我想是的。
- Yeah, nothing really bad happened.
- 是的，并没有发生什么坏事。
- I shaved my head!
- 我把头发剃光了！
For real!
真的！
- Ooh. - Wow.
- 哦。 - 哇。
- Yikes. - Your hair really is everything.
- 哎呀。 - 你的头发真的很重要。
- Your real bald head has taught us all a lesson.
你光秃秃的脑袋给我们大家都上了一课。
We could all work on respecting each other's privacy
我们都可以努力尊重彼此的隐私
so this sort of thing never happens again.
这样事情就不会再发生了。
- Dawn's right.
- 道恩说得对。
Who wants cinnamon rolls?
谁想吃肉桂卷？
- Oh, yum, me. - Yeah.
- 哦，好吃，我要。- 是的。
- I shaved my head!
- 我剃了头！
- Looking good, kids.
- 孩子们，看起来不错。
- Did we all really have to shave our heads?
- 我们都必须剃头吗？
- Hey, quad for all, and all for bald.
- 嘿，四人同行，共赴光头。
- Besides, I'm sure it'll grow back.
- 再说，我肯定它会再长出来的。
- Maybe. - [gasps]
- 也许吧。 - [吸气声]
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪